igodigital.com 2014-03-10

# None

## iGoDigital Privacy, Security, and Application Accessibility Policy

Last Revised November 2013

### Information Collection and Use

We may collect the following types of information:

**Personal Contact Information** – Any personal information provided on an iGoDigital site or application is used solely as a collection point for our clients. Your name, address, telephone number, gender, age, or any other personal information is not stored in any of iGoDigital’s databases or on any iGoDigital server. This information will not be sent to our client without your consent or authorization. iGoDigital stores any information pertinent to the application (including but not limited to answers, results, and any requests or interaction with the tools). This information is cross­‐referenced to a secure, unique General User Identification ( _guid_ ). Within policy standards of our clients and your permission, iGoDigital may store an email address associated with the _guid_.

**Cookies** – iGoDigital will store one or more cookies on your computer or mobile device when you visit our tool or application. We use cookies to improve the quality of your experience, including enhanced browsing experiences, place‐holding, and non‐personal application data. We do not use the cookie to store personal or private data.

**Log information** – When you access an iGoDigital service via a browser, application or other client, our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

**Third Party Applications** – iGoDigital rarely utilizes third party applications. If these applications require information, we will obtain your consent before submitting this information to the application. The information collected by iGoDigital when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies.

**Location data** – Some iGoDigital applications require location data. iGoDigital obtains this information using your computer's IP address in conjunction with Domain Registrations and Internet Service Provider IP registrations. This information may be stored as part of the anonymous user _guid_. This data is only used to enhance or personalize your site experience.

**Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to iGoDigital services only. Our clients’ sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

iGoDigital processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information outside your own country.

### Information Sharing

iGoDigital does not store any personal information directly related to an individual. However, the analytical nature of our personalization allows us to create unique individual profiles. A collection of these profiles can be used to create demographic data. This data may be shared with our clients or similar agencies. These companies would not have the means to contact you or identify you individually. In the case where a tool may need to store your email address, this email address is expunged before data is shared with a Client or Third Party.

If the event would ever occur that iGoDigital would be required to share personal information with other companies or individuals outside of iGoDigital, it will fall in the following limited circumstances: We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of iGoDigital, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to all information to a restrictive group of iGoDigital employees. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

#### Accessing Data

If your tool data, results, or interaction is displayed on another domain, website, or URL outside of iGoDigital’s control, the data provided is under your consent. By using an iGoDigital tool, you authorize iGoDigital’s client to access and display that data back to you. This data, while containing no personal data; is sent over a secured data transfer line. The data is referenced only by the anonymous user _guid_ and would require data from both parties to align a user to the data.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

### Accessibility

iGoDigital is aware of all web users. We strive to bring an experience on the Internet that can be enjoyed by everyone sitting at a computer screen. Whenever possible, iGoDigital builds their tools and applications according to the [2010 ADA STANDARDS FOR ACCESSIBLE DESIGN.](http://www.ada.gov/2010ADAstandards_index.htm "2010 ADA Standards for Design")

We strive to be the industry leader in web site design and architecture. However, being on the edge comes at a price. We know universal usability is paramount to successful web tools and applications. We always conform to the latest W3 standards, but will usually push the envelope when needed. The latest W3 Standards can be found [here](http://www.w3.org/standards/ "W3 Standards").
